<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="title">
        <item> A - Apple </item>
        <item> B - Banana </item>
        <item> C - Cat </item>
        <item> D - Dog </item>
        <item> E - Elephant </item>
        <item> F - Fish </item>
        <item> G - Goat </item>
        <item> H - Horse </item>
        <item> I - Ice Cream </item>
        <item> J - Jackal </item>
        <item> K - Koala</item>
        <item> L - Lion </item>
        <item> M - Mango</item>
        <item> N - Nest </item>
        <item> O - Orange </item>
        <item> P - Peafowl </item>
        <item> Q - Queen </item>
        <item> R - Rat </item>
        <item> S - Strawberry </item>
        <item> T - Tomato </item>
        <item> U - Umbrella </item>
        <item> V - Violin </item>
        <item> W - Watermelon </item>
        <item> X - Xylophone</item>
        <item> Y - Yak </item>
        <item> Z - Zebra </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="introduction">
        <item> <!-- Apple -->
            1. An apple is a sweet, edible fruit produced by an apple tree (Malus domestica).\n
            2. The fruit matures in late summer or autumn, and cultivars exist in a wide range of sizes.\n
            3. The skin of ripe apples is generally red, yellow, green, pink, or russetted, though many bi- or tri-colored cultivars may be found
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Banana -->
            1. A banana is an edible fruit. (botanically a berry).\n
            2. The banana plant is the largest herbaceous flowering plant.\n
            3. The skin of ripe bananas is generally green, yellow, red, purple, or brown.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Cat-->
            1. The cat is a domestic species of small carnivorous mammal.\n
            2. Domestic cats are valued by humans for companionship and their ability to hunt rodents.\n
            3. Cats can have kittens from spring to late autumn.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Dog-->
            1. A dog is a carnivore animal. \n
            2. It is the most widely abundant terrestrial carnivore.\n
            3. Their lives ranges from 10 to 13 years.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Elephant -->
            1. Elephants are mammals of the family Elephantidae and the largest existing land animals.\n
            2. Tusks, which are derived from the incisor teeth, serve both as weapons and as tools for moving objects and digging.\n
            3. They are considered to be keystone species, due to their impact on their environments.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Fish -->
            1. Fish are gill-bearing aquatic craniate animals that lack limbs with digits.\n
            2. The earliest organisms that can be classified as fish were soft-bodied chordates that first appeared during the Cambrian period.\n
            3. Fish can communicate in their underwater environments through the use of acoustic communication.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Goat -->
            1. The domestic goat or simply goat is a subspecies of C. aegagrus domesticated from the wild goat of Southwest Asia and Eastern Europe.\n
            2. The goat is a member of the animal family Bovidae and the subfamily Caprinae, meaning it is closely related to the sheep.\n
            3. There are over 300 distinct breeds of goat.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Horse -->
            1. Horse is an odd-toed ungulate mammal belonging to the taxonomic family Equidae.\n
            2. There are more than 300 breeds of horse in the world today.\n
            3. Depending on breed, management and environment, the modern domestic horse has a life expectancy of 25 to 30 years.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Ice cream -->
            1. Ice cream (derived from earlier iced cream or cream ice) is a sweetened frozen food typically eaten as a snack or dessert.\n
            2. It may be made from dairy milk or cream and is flavoured with a sweetener, either sugar or an alternative, and any spice, such as cocoa or vanilla.\n
            3. Ice cream is considered a colloidal system.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Jackal-->
            1. Jackals are medium-sized omnivorous mammals.\n
            2. Jackals are opportunistic omnivores, predators of small to medium-sized animals and proficient scavengers.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Koala -->
            1. The koala or, inaccurately, koala bear is an arboreal herbivorous marsupial native to Australia.\n
            2. They are found in coastal areas of the mainland\'s eastern and southern regions, inhabiting Queensland, New South Wales, Victoria, and South Australia.\n
            3. The koala is a stocky animal with a large head and vestigial or non-existent tail.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Lion -->
            1. The lion is a wild animal, usually found in forests. \n
            2. A lion pride consists of a few adult males, related females and cubs.\n
            3. Groups of female lions usually hunt together, preying mostly on large ungulates.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Mango -->
            1. A mango is a juicy stone fruit produced from numerous species of tropical trees.\n
            2. Mangoes are native to South Asia.\n
            3. Mango trees grow to 35–40 m (115–131 ft) tall.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Nest -->
            1. A nest is a structure built by certain animals to hold eggs, offspring, and, occasionally, the animal itself.\n
            2. They may be composed of organic material such as twigs, grass, and leaves.\n
            3. Nest building is driven by a biological urge known as the nesting instinct in birds and mammals.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Orange -->
            1. The orange is the fruit of the citrus species Citrus - sinensis in the family Rutaceae, native to China.\n
            2. The orange is a hybrid between pomelo (Citrus maxima) and mandarin (Citrus reticulata).\n
            3. Orange trees are widely grown in tropical and subtropical climates for their sweet fruit.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Peacock -->
            1. Male peafowl are referred to as peacocks.\n
            2. Female peafowl as peahens.\n
            3. Peafowl are omnivores and eat mostly plants, flower petals, seed heads, insects and other arthropods, reptiles, and amphibians.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Queen -->
            1. Queen is known as the head of a respective country.\n
            2. She generally rules the whole country.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Rats -->
            1. Rats are various medium-sized, long-tailed rodents.\n
            2. Rats are typically distinguished from mice by their size.\n
            3. Rats have long been considered deadly pests.
        </item>
        <item>  <!-- Strawberry -->
            1. It is a fruit which is red in colour.\n
            2. For purposes of commercial production, plants are propagated from runners and, in general, distributed as either bare root plants or plugs.\n
            3. It has lower investment costs, and lower overall maintenance requirements.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Tomato -->
            1. The tomato is the edible, often red, berry of the plant Solanum lycopersicum, commonly known as a tomato plant.\n
            2. Tomatoes are a significant source of umami flavor.\n
            3. Numerous varieties of the tomato plant are widely grown in temperate climates across the world.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Umbrella -->
            1. An umbrella or parasol is a folding canopy.\n
            2. It is made by wooden or metal ribs that is usually mounted on a wooden, metal, or plastic pole.\n
            3. The term umbrella is traditionally used when protecting oneself from rain.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Violin -->
            1. The violin, sometimes known as a fiddle, is a wooden string instrument in the violin family.\n
            2. Most violins have a hollow wooden body.\n
            3. They are most prominent in the Western classical tradition, both in ensembles (from chamber music to orchestras) and as solo instruments.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Watermelon -->
            1. Watermelon (Citrullus lanatus) is a plant species in the family Cucurbitaceae, a vine-like flowering plant originally domesticated in West Africa.\n
            2. The sweet, juicy flesh is usually deep red to pink, with many black seeds, although seedless varieties exist.\n
            3. It is commonly consumed as a juice or as an ingredient in mixed beverages.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Xylophone -->
            1. The xylophone word is taken from the Greek words.\n
            2. It is a musical instrument in the percussion family that consists of wooden bars struck by mallets.\n
            3. The instrument has obscure ancient origins.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Yak -->
            1. The domestic yak (Bos grunniens) is a long-haired domesticated bovid.\n
            2. It is generally found throughout the Himalayan region of the Indian subcontinent, the Tibetan Plateau, Northern Myanmar, Yunnan, Sichuan and as far north as Mongolia and Siberia.\n
            3. It is descended from the wild yak.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Zebra -->
            1. Zebras (horse family) united by their distinctive black-and-white striped coats.\n
            2. Their stripes come in different patterns, unique to each individual.\n
            3. They are generally social animals that live in small harems to large herds.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="wikipedia">
        <item> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Apple </item>
        <item> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Banana </item>
        <item> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cat </item>
        <item> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dog </item>
        <item> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Elephant </item>
        <item> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fish </item>
        <item> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Goat </item>
        <item> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Horse </item>
        <item> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ice_cream </item>
        <item> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jackal </item>
        <item> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Koala </item>
        <item> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lion </item>
        <item> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mango </item>
        <item> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nest </item>
        <item> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Orange_(fruit) </item>
        <item> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Peafowl </item>
        <item> https://dictionary.cambridge.org/dictionary/english/queen </item>
        <item> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rat </item>
        <item> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Strawberry </item>
        <item> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tomato </item>
        <item> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Umbrella </item>
        <item> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Violin </item>
        <item> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Watermelon </item>
        <item> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Xylophone </item>
        <item> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Domestic_yak </item>
        <item> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Zebra </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>